nuwber.com 2017-03-19

# Privacy Policy

By accessing or using the website available at <https://nuwber.com/> (the “Website”) each Website user (“you”) agrees and acknowledges to be bound by this Privacy Policy (“Policy”).

This Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use information your device or your browser provides to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using the Website.

#### 1\. Information Available Through Website

We aggregate (the same way as Google or other search engines do) information that is already in free access, has been made available by people or with their consent, and openly circulates on the Internet. This information is available to you and other Website users through the people search on the Website.

We do not own, create, enter, filter, process or verify this information about people. We do not evaluate each entry and make no guarantees to you about the accuracy of any information or how recently any information was collected or updated.

We only collect information about your use of the Website as described further in this Policy.

**Information available through the Website is not part of Usage Data collected by us and covered by this Policy, or part of Personal Data as referred to in this Policy.**

To request that information about you be removed from the Website’s people search, please use our opt-out tool at <https://nuwber.com/removal/link>. This tool is only intended to remove information available through Nuwber and cannot remove the information from the third-party sources.

#### 2\. Use of Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to collect information about your use of the Website. Google Analytics collects only non-personally identifiable information about your usage of the Website that alone or in combination with similar information can not be used to identify you as an individual from your device and/or browser when you access and use the Website (“Usage Data”).

Google Analytics collects Usage Data such as:

  * how often users visit the Website,
  * what pages they visit when they do so,
  * what other sites they used prior to coming to the Website,
  * the type of device used,
  * browser type and language,
  * version, language and type of users’ operating system,
  * the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit the Website, rather than your name or other identifying information.

We use Usage Data we get from Google Analytics for:

  * For analytical and statistical purposes,
  * To understand your interaction with the Website, and
  * For further improvement and development of the Website.

We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with your Personal Data (since we do not collect it in the first place).

Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Website is restricted by the [ _Google Analytics Terms of Use_](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) (as [ _amended for government websites_](http://www.howto.gov/sites/default/files/google-analytics-tos-amendment.pdf)) and the [ _Google Privacy Policy_](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). For more information on Google Analytics, please visit [_Google Analytics_](http://www.google.com/analytics/) website.

#### 3\. Information We Do Not Collect

WE DO NOT COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL DATA, which is information or its combination that can be used to identify you as an individual. We do not process and collect any Personal Data or personally identifiable information, unless you specifically decide to provide such information (such as by emailing to us) and you have the choice (and we urge you) not to disclose any Personal Data to us.

#### 4\. Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your computer by websites including this one. Cookies usually contain anonymous information which can only be accessed by the website which placed it on your computer.

Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit the Website. Google Analytics uses only first-party cookies for data analysis. This means that the cookies are linked to a specific website domain, and Google Analytics will only use that cookie data for statistical analysis related to your browsing behavior on that specific website. According to Google, the data collected cannot be altered or retrieved by services from other domains. Basically, this cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google.

We do not use cookies to track your use of the Internet in any way or to store any Personal Data.

This Policy covers use of cookies only by Google Analytics and does not cover the use of cookies by any other third parties. We do not control when or how other third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, third party websites to which a link or advertisement points may set cookies on your computer. Some of these services may be used to track your behavior on other websites and we have no control over this.

You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to the Website by [ _disabling cookies_](http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml) on your browser.

If you choose, you can opt out by turning off cookies in the preferences settings in your web browser.

#### 5\. Use of Google Maps

We use Google Maps APIs to provide map information and photographic imagery. All the photos you can see on people search results pages are provided by Google Maps.

This Policy incorporates [_the Google Privacy Policy_](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) as amended by Google from time to time.

#### 6\. Other Third-Party Websites and Services

Third parties may collect your Usage Data. There are a number of places on or through the Website where you may click on a link to access other websites, services or web resources that are not affiliated or connected with us and do not operate under this Policy. For example, if you click on an ad or a link, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may independently collect information, including your Personal Data, from you. We advise you to check the privacy policies of all third-party websites you visit.

We may allow third-party advertising companies or ad networks to display advertisements or place ad tags on the Websites. We do not provide any Personal Data to these companies. These third-party companies may use tracking tools, such as cookies, to collect Usage Data and other information about computers used to view or interact with their ads.

#### 7\. With Whom We Share Usage Data

We may share aggregated Usage Data with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and contractors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of users of the Website and the most popular features or services accessed.

This Policy does not limit in any way our use or disclosure of Usage Data and we reserve the right to use and disclose such Usage Data to our partners, advertisers and other third parties at our discretion.

#### 8\. Information Concerning Children

We do not knowingly collect or solicit any Personal Data from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to use the Website. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take immediate steps to remove that information.

#### 9\. Information Security

We will take commercially reasonable precautions to protect Usage Data from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. We process all Usage Data using industry-standard techniques. We store Usage Data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted. However, we do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to Usage Data that we store.

#### 10\. Severability and Integration

This Policy constitutes the entire agreement between you and us and supersedes all previous written or oral agreements. If any part of the Policy is held invalid or unenforceable, that portion shall be construed in a manner consistent with applicable law to reflect, as nearly as possible, the original intentions of the parties, and the remaining portions shall remain in full force and effect.

#### 11\. Changes to the Policy

We may change the Policy at any time. You can review the most current version of the Policy available at <https://nuwber.com/policy>. If you continue to use the website after we make changes to the Policy, you are signifying your acceptance of the new terms. You are responsible for checking this Policy periodically for any changes.

#### 12\. Business or Asset Transfer

In the event that we, a line of our business, or substantially all our assets are transferred, sold or merged with another business, Usage Data may be one of the transferred assets.

#### 13\. Privacy Related Inquiries

If you have questions about the collection of Usage Data, please, contact us at [support@nuwber.com](mailto:support@nuwber.com).

**Last updated: September 28, 2016**
